Guide to the Stanley Dance and Helen Oakley Dance Papers
Yale University Music Library
- Photographs
  - Group photos
    - Carney, Harry with Billy Strayhorn. Also P. Sambamurthi, Musiri Subramania Ayyar [i.e., Iyer], Albert Franklin, Sonny Green, Herbie Fields, Johnny Hodges, Lawrence Brown, Toby Harwwick, Tucky Sam Hunter, Shelton Hemphill, Jimmy Hamilton, Joe Nanton, Russell Procope, and others (Box 41)
    - Carry, Scoops with Earl Hines and his Orchestra (Box 41)
    - Casey, Al with John Williams. Also Max Jones. (Box 41)
    - Champlin, Charles (Box 41)
    - Charles, Ray with Cleo Harne (Box 41)
    - Cheatham, Doc with Wilbor De Paris. Also Simonson, Dick Campbell, Wilbert Kirk, Omer Simeon, Gerald Reeves, Joe Duff, Bill Woods, Count Turner, "Fat Man" Turner, Warner Seals, Jerry Blake, Clark Terry, Benny Carter, and others (Box 41)
    - Cheatham, Jimmy with Jeannie Cheatham and Jay Mcshann (Box 41)
    - Clayton, Buck with Count Basie, Jack Washington, and Herschel Evans. Also, Buddy Tate, Ship Hall, Dicky Wells, Rudy Rutherford, Mary Osborne, Tyree Glenn, Earle Warren, Stanley Dance, Joe Newman, Freddie Green, Vic Dickenson, Woody Herman, and Sammy Price (Box 41)
    - Cole, Cozy with D Barker, Cab Calloway, Chu Berry, and Huet Hunter. Also Dick Clarke, Taft Jordan, Gene Krupa, and Edgar Battle. (Box 41)
    - Coles, Ronnie with Bill Pemburton (Box 41)
    - Connors, Chuck with Johnny Hodges, and Booty Wood (Box 41)
    - Cook, Willie with Johnny Hodges, Russell Procope and Paul Gonzalves (Box 41)
    - Corea, Chick with Herbie Hancock (Box 41)
    - Crawford, Jimmy with Bob Kreider, Joe Thomas, and Timmie Rogers. Also, Stanley Dance, Betty Kreider, Mrs. Thomas, Mrs. Crawford, and Jimmie Lunceford (Box 41)
    - Cray, Robert with Johnny Copeland and Albert Collins (Box 41)
    - Crimbley, Elmer with Babe Clark, Money Johnson, and LaVern Barker (Box 41)
    - Dance, Helen with Benny Carter, 1994 (Box 41)
    - Dance, Stanley with Joe Thomas, Sammy Price, and Buster Bailey. Also, Ed Allen, Rolf Ericson, Clark Terry, Erroll Garner, John Hammond, Jerry Gray, Dan Morgenstern, Pauline Rivelli, Bob Thiele, Shirley Conover, Willis Conover, Aaron Bell, Johnny Hodges, Patricia Willard, and Chet Camuchall (Box 41)
    - Davis, Eddie "Lockjaw" with Bobby Plater. Also, Stanley Dance, Joe Thomas, Ronnie Scott, Grover Mitchell, and John Puelr [sic] (Box 41)
    - Davis, Miles with Wayne Shorter (Box 41)
    - Dickenson, Vic with Charlie Shavers. Also Hilton Jefferson, Herman Autrey, Yannick Bruynoghe, Dan Morgenstern, Buck Clayton, Earle Warren, Roy Eldridge, Gene Ramey, and Bud Freeman (Box 41)
    - Dixon, Eric with Kenny Hung. Also Bobby Plater and John Williams (Box 41)
    - Dixon, George with Alvin Burroughs. Also Perkins and others (Box 41)
    - Dixon, Willie (Box 41)
    - Dorsey, George, [Dave] McRae, and Unknown, 1957 (Box 41)
    - Dorsey, Tommy (Box 41)
    - Dunlap, Louis with Charles Carpenter (Box 41)
    - Edison, Harry with Benny Carter. Also Clark Terry (Box 41)
    - Eldridge, Roy with Israel Crosby. Also Johnny Guarnieri, Cozy Cole, and Franz Jackson (Box 41)
    - Ellington, Mercer with Stanley Dance, Paul Gonsalves, Russel Procope, and Helen Procope. Also Wild Bill Davis, Billy Eckstine, Sarah Vaughan, David Brubeck, Charles Mingus, Joe Williams, Cootie Williams, Juan Tizol, Lawrence Brown and others. (Box 41)
    - Ellis, Donald with John Hammond, Clive J. Davis and others (Box 41)
    - Evans, Bill with Helen Keane, and Teo Macero. Also Tony Bennett. (Box 41)
    - Evans, Gil with Helen Merrill. Also Tadd Dameron (Box 41)
    - Feather, Leonard with Stanley Dance (Box 41)
    - Fitzgerald, Ella with Billy Kyle and Chick Webb. Also Sarah Jones, Bobby Burnett, Stuff Smith, Sandy Williams, Eddie Barfield, Mouse Randolph, Taft Jordan, Geo Matthews, Teddy McRae, Chauncey Haughton, Dick Vance, Short Baker, Clark Terry, and others (Box 41)
    - Fuller, Walter (Box 41)
    - Garner, Erroll with Roy Eldridge (Box 41)
    - Gee, Matthew with Al Lucas, Sam Woodyard, Aaron Bell, Ray Copeland, Eddie Bert, Haywood Henry, Joe Evans, Buddy Terry, and others (Box 41)
    - George, Karl with Joe Newman, Dexter Gordon, and Fred Bechett (Box 41)
    - Getz, Stanley with Chet Baker (Box 41)
    - Gillespie, Dizzy with Milt Hinton and Billy Taylor. Also, James Moody, Frank Schifano, and Candy Finch (Box 41)
    - Glenn, Tyree with Chuck Cannas, Kai Winding, Stanley Dance, and Johnny Hodges (Box 41)
    - Gonsalves, Paul with Benny Powell and Budd Johnson. Also, Esther Marrow, Sonny Criss, Russell Procope, Harold Ashby, Sam Jones, Eddie Locke, Roy Eldridge, Cliff Smalls, Stanley Dance, and Michael James (Box 41)
    - Goodman, Benny with Chick Webb and Joe Bushkin. Also, Lionel Hampton, Teddy Wilson, Chu Berry, Buster Bailey, Fletcher Henderson, Helen Ward, Helen Oakley Dance, Ben Pollack, Glenn Burrs, and Carl Coms (Box 41)
    - Gorrill, Liz with Andy Fite (Box 41)
    - Grappelli, Stephane with Bill Coleman (Box 41)
    - Green, Freddie with Count Basie (Box 41)
    - Gregory, Dick with Paul Bascomb (Box 41)
    - Grusin, Dave with Don Grusin. Also, Frances W. Preston and Rick Riccobono (Box 41)
    - Hackett, Bobby with Doc Cheatham (Box 41)
    - Hall, Juanita with Jimmy Crawford, Doc Cheatham, Buster Bailey, Coleman Hawkins, Claude Hopkins, and Georgr Duvivier (Box 41)
    - Hamilton, Jimmy with Willie Cook, Alice Babs, and Bob Wilber (Box 41)
    - Hammond, John with Benny Goodman, Goddard Lieberson, John Wexler, Robert Fertig, Jon Waxman, Chris Albertson, Bob Altshuler, and Larry Hiller (Box 41)
    - Hampton, Lionel with Herbie Hancock and Frances Preston. Also, Stanley Dance (Box 41)
    - Hardwick, Otto with Harry Carney (Box 41)
    - Harris, Dicky with Sammy Lowe and Mrs. Dud Bascomb (Box 41)
    - Hawkins, Coleman with Thelonius Monk. Also, Hank Jones, George Arvanitas, Jimmy Woode, Kansas Fields, Micky Baker, Eddie Locke, Sam Woodyard, Roy Eldridge, and Truck Parham (Box 41)
    - Haywood, Cedric with Alom Burroughs and Hog (Box 41)
    - Henderson, Fletcher with Charlie Barnet (Box 41)
    - Henderson, Luther with Leonard de Paur (Box 41)
    - Hinton, Milt with Coleman Hawkins. Also, Margo Broynoohe (Box 41)
    - Hodges, Johnny with Billy Strayhorn and Stanley Dance. Also, Harry Carney, Lawrence Brown, Madeleine Gautier, Paul Gonsalves, Harold Ashby, Benny Carter, Edith Cue Hodges, Russell Procope, John Sanders, and Oliver Nelson (Box 41)
    - Holiday, Billie with Snooky Young (Box 41)
    - Hopkins, Claude with Doc Cheatham, Buster Bailey, Coleman Hawkins, Juanita Hall, Jimmy Crawford, and Duovier (Box 41)
    - Hopkins, "Lightnin'" with Otis Spann (Box 41)
    - Hopkins, Linda with Caroline Peyton (Box 41)
    - Hucko, Peanuts with Rex Stewart (Box 41)
    - Hughes, Bill with Grover Mitchell (Box 41)
    - Humes, Helen with Red Norvo, Geo Benson, Barney Morton [sic], Benny Carter, Jo Jones, Milt Hinton, and Gerry Wiggins (Box 41)
    - Illinois, Jacquet with Dexter Gordon, Ray Perry, and Marshal Royal (Box 42)
    - James, Leon with Al Minns (Box 42)
    - Jarvis, Al with Wm Pyatt [sic] (Box 42)
    - Jefferson, Hilton with Buster Bailey, Gene Ramey, Vic Dickenson, and Charlie Shavers (Box 42)
    - Jenkins, Freddie with [indecipherable] Jacobs (Box 42)
    - Jenkins, Pat with Dicky Wells and Eli Robinson. Also, Stanley Dance, Ben Richardson, Buddy Tate,and Joe Benjamin (Box 42)
    - Jester, James L. with Hayes Pillars (Box 42)
    - Jinda, George with Chieli Minucci (Box 42)
    - Johnson, Bobby with Bobby Green (Box 42)
    - Johnson, Budd with Claude Hopkins. Also, Willie Randall, Madeleine Green, and Leroy Harris (Box 42)
    - Johnson, Howard with Stanley Dance and Lawrence Lucie (Box 42)
    - Johnson, J.J. with Kai Winding (Box 42)
    - Johnson, Money with Les Erskine, Frank Wess, Frank Skeete, Bull Moose Jackson, Head Adams, and Bill Mann (Box 42)
    - Jolson, Al with Ruby Keeler (Box 42)
    - Jones, Claude with Keg Johnson (Box 42)
    - Jones, Etta with Billy Eckstine, King Curtis, and The Isley Brothers (Box 42)
    - Jones, Hank with Al Hibbler (Box 42)
    - Jones, Jimmy with Joe Thomas and Billy Taylor (Box 42)
    - Jones, Jo (Jonathan) with Major "Mune" Holley. Also, Al Murray and Count Basie (Box 42)
    - Jones, Jonah with Dave Riviera, Milt Hinton, and Panama Francis. Also, Keg Johnson, Hilton Jefferson, Sam Taylor, Jerome Darr, Teddy Brannon, Red Sanders, Pinky Tomlin, Joe Bushkin, Clark Terry, and Wild Bill Davison (Box 42)
    - Jones, Quincy with George Benson (Box 42)
    - Jones, Wallace with Rex Stuart and Cootie Williams (Box 42)
    - Jungheim, Ralph with Stanley Dance (Box 42)
    - Kelly, George with Henry Haywood (Box 42)
    - Kelly, Wynton with Dizzy Gillespie and Paul Gonsalves (Box 42)
    - Kenton, Stan with Bob Kreider. Also, Chan Parker, Bob Share [sic] Stanley Dance, and Shirley Conover (Box 42)
    - Kessel, Barney with Benny Carter (Box 42)
    - Khan, Chaka with Bobby Bland and B.B. King (Box 42)
    - King, B.B. with Charles Brooks, Leo Lanchie, and Sid Filler. Also, Esther Marrow, Keith Braton, Wendell Sawyer, Richard Pratt, Theodore Mills, and [Vernon] Sawyer (Box 42)
    - Ladner, Calvin with James "Buddy" Bolden, Money Johnson, and Barry Lee Hall (Box 42)
    - Laine, Cleo with John Dankworth (Box 42)
    - Larkins, Ellis with Al Hall (Box 42)
    - LaRocca, Nick with Bunny Berigan, and Nat and Lloyd Williams (Box 42)
    - Laswell, Bill with Peter Brotzmann, Ronald Shannon Jackson, and Sonny Sharrock (Box 42)
    - Lawson, Yank with Bob Haggart (Box 42)
    - Leon, Craig with Cassell Webb (Box 42)
    - Lewis, John with Richard Nixon, Prudent Nixon, Milt Jackson, Stanley Dance, and The Shah of Iran (Box 42)
    - Love, Preston with Leo Kraft (Box 42)
    - Lovelle, Herbie with Buddy Tate and Stanley Dance (Box 42)
    - McGhee, Brownie with Sonny Terry (Box 42)
    - McPartland, Marian with Bobby Short and Cecil Taylor. Also, George Shearing, Judy Roberts, McCoy Tyner, Dorothy Donegan, Kenny Kirkland, Roy "Little Jazz" Eldridge, Steve Allen, Dudley Moore, Henry Mancini, Carmen McRae, Dizzy Gillespie, Cleo Brown, Darnelle and George Wein, Peter Nero, and Dave Brubeck (Box 42)
    - McRae, Carmen with Roger Kellaway (Box 42)
    - McShann, Jay with Gene Ramey and Gus Johnson. Also, Buddy Tate, Paul Quinichette, Joe Newman, and Bruce Ricker (Box 42)
    - Maxwell, Jimmy with J.C. Heard, Barney Bigard, and Vic Dickenson (Box 42)
    - Mehegan, John with John Sanders, Stanley Dance, George Simon, and Newman O'Connor (Box 42)
    - Mitchell, Grover with Henderson Chambers, and Al Grey. Also, Jack Jeffers, Kenny Hing, Danny Turner, Bobby Plater, and Joe Temperley (Box 42)
    - Mitchell, Red with Bill Mays (Box 42)
    - Monk, Thelonius with Richard Stoltzman (Box 42)
    - Mooney, Art with Bob Kreider (Box 42)
    - Morello, Joe with Gene Wright (Box 42)
    - Morgenstern, Dan with Bob Kaiser and Art Hodes. Also, Stanley Dance and others (Box 42)
    - Morris, Johnnie with Al Jarvis and Charlie Frazier (Box 42)
    - Mosley, Snub with Syrup, Giles, Eddie Baufield, and Al Bowlly (Box 42)
    - Mulligan, Gerry with Chet Baker (Box 42)
    - Mundy, Jimmy with Jimmy Rushing and Nat Pierce (Box 42)
    - Nance, Ray with Spencer Odom, O. Coleman, and Leroy Harris. Also, John Hardee, Harry Edison, Max Roach, Stanley [Dance], Gene Ammons, and Tony [Gomez] (Box 42)
    - Nanton, Tricky Sam with Barney Bigard. Also, Artie Whetsol, Juan Tizol, and Lawrence Brown (Box 42)
    - Newton, Frankie with Jo Jones, Freddie Green, Ed Lewis, Walter Page, and Dan Minor (Box 42)
    - Norman, Fred with Stump Brady and Vic Dickenson (Box 42)
    - Nicholas, Big Nick with Snub Mosely and Joe Thomas (Box 42)
    - O'Brien, Floyd with Jim Gordon and Eddie Miller. Also, Yank Lawson and Matty Mattock (Box 42)
    - Oliver, Sy with Cliff Smalls (Box 42)
    - Ory, Kid with Andrew Blakeney and Bob McCracken (Box 42)
    - Otis, Johnny with Shuggie Otis and others (Box 42)
    - Panassié, Hugues with Madeleine Gautier and Louis Armstrong (Box 42)
    - Parker, Charlie with Dizzy Gillespie. Also, Charlie Shavers, Benny Carter, Ben Webster, Johnny Hodges, anf Flip Phillips (Box 42)
    - Perez-Prado with Doc Cheatham, Paul Webster, Jose Granata, and Ulasho (Olacio) Rabinowitz (Box 42)
    - Powell, Mel with Chuck Riggs (Box 42)
    - Powell, Rudy with Danny Barker (Box 42)
    - Powell, Seldon with Aaron Bell (Box 42)
    - Pruitt, Carl with Thelonius Monk and Jerome Richardson (Box 42)
    - Quinichette, Paul with Gene Ramey. Also Joe Newman and Buddy Tate (Box 42)
    - Ramey, Gene with Jay McShann, Jimmy Rushing, and Buddy Tate. Also, Andy Kirk, Floyd Ray, Buddy Anderson, Shirley Green, Fred Higgins, Little John, Walter Brown, Tay Dance, Rudolph "Schoolboy" Dennis, Paul Quinichette, Alonzo Peltiford, Eddie Cleanhead Vinson, Paul Gunther, Lester Young, Jo Jones, Gus Johnson, John Jackson, and Jimmy Coe (Box 43)
    - Ramirez, Ram with Ernie Shipard, Jimmy Hamilton, and Paul Gonsalves. Also, Brook Benton, Frank Diggs, Walter Schoop, Stanley Dance, Buck Clayton, Eddie Durham, and Wilma Dobie (Box 43)
    - Redd, Gene with Gene Wells and Carl Pruitt (Box 43)
    - Redd, Vi with Dizzy Gillespie (Box 43)
    - Redman, Don with Shorty Baker (Box 43)
    - Richardson, Ben with Pat Jenkins (Box 42)
    - Richardson, Jerome with Wendell Marshall, Seldon Powell, Zoot Sims, Howard Johnson, Herbie Lovelle, Quentin Jackson, Britt Woodman, Clark Terry, and Taft Jordan (Box 43)
    - Ritenour, Lee with Justo Almario (Box 43)
    - Roberts, Luckey with Willie "The Lion" Smith (Box 43)
    - Robillard, Duke with Greg Piccolo and Preston Hubbard (Box 43)
    - Rodney, Red with Lennie Niehaus, Charles McPherson, Burt Korall, and Jean Banks (Box 43)
    - Rouse, Charlie with Ben Riley, Thelonius Monk, and Larry Gales (Box 43)
    - Rowles, Jimmie with Wendell Lowe and Nellie Luther (Box 43)
    - Rushing, Jimmy with Coleman Hawkins and Vic Dickenson. Also, Wendell Marshall, Seldon Powell, Herbie Lovelle, Zoot Sims, Howard Johnson, Clark Terry, Quentin Jackson, Taft Jordan, Britt Woodman, Jerome Richardson, John Levy, Earle Warren, Teddy Wilson, Sir Charles Thompson, Stanley Dance, and Dicky Wells (Box 43)
    - Russell, Johnny with Bobby Martin, Bass Hill, Glyn Pacque, and Roger Ramirez (Box 43)
    - Sadie, Stanley with H. Wiley Hitchcock and Susan Feder (Box 43)
    - Santana, Carlos with John Lee Hooker (Box 43)
    - Scott, Ronnie with Eddie "Lockjaw" Davis (Box 43)
    - Sears, Al with Budd Johnson (Box 43)
    - Sedric, Gene with Red Allen (Box 43)
    - Sharrock, Sonny with Linda Sharrock (Box 43)
    - Shavers, Charlie with Vic Dickenson (Box 43)
    - Sheen, Mickey with Coleman Hawkins and Hank Jones (Box 43)
    - Shields, Larry with Pete Pomiglio, Ward Leigh, and others (Box 43)
    - Singleton, Zutty with Eddie Barefield, J.C. [Higgmilton], Cliff Jackson, Henry Goodwin, Zutty Singleton, and Hayes Willis (Box 43)
    - Smith, Greg with Bev Smith (Box 43)
    - Smith, Steve with Heywood Brown (Box 43)
    - Smith, Willie with Timmy Young, Joe Thomas, and Gerald Corbon. Also, Tommy Gumina, Harry Lim, and Bill Perkins (Box 43)
    - Smith, Willie "The Lion", with Eddie Barefield, J.C. [Higgmilton] and Jack Butler (Box 43)
    - Spanier, Muggsy with Darnell Howard (Box 43)
    - Stewart, Rex with Tyree Glenn. Also, Cootie Williams and Artie Whetsol (Box 43)
    - Stewart, Slam with Major Holley. Also, Claire Stewart and Red Norvo (Box 43)
    - Sullivan, Joe with Earl Hines and Muggsy Spanier (Box 43)
    - Sylvian, David with Holger Czukay (Box 43)
    - Szabó, Gábor with Bob Thiele (Box 43)
    - Tabackin, Lew with Toshiko Akioshi (Box 43)
    - Tate, Buddy with Eli Robinson, Ben Richardson, and Pat Jenkins. Also, Herbie Lovelle, Everett Barksdale, Ship Neill, Coleman Hawkins, Danny Barker, Rudy Powell, Jimmy Rushing, Jo Jones, Ben Webster, Ben Coleman, Vic Dickenson, Count Basie, Dicky Wells, Dud and Paul Bascomb, Harry Edison, Ben Wilber, Clark Terry, Kenny Davison, and others (Box 43)
    - Tatum, Art with Henry Parker, and [Jets] Weller. Also, Bill Douglas and Red Callender (Box 43)
    - Taylor, Billy, with Leonard Bernstein (Box 43)
    - Taylor, Billy Sr. with Jonah Jones. Also, Buddy Tate, Clark Terry, and Joe Thomas (Box 43)
    - Taylor, Billy Jr. with Jonah Jones and Billy Strayhorn (Box 43)
    - Teagarden, Jack with Dick Shannon and Peck Kelle (Box 43)
    - Teagle, Birch with Billy Taylor (Box 43)
    - Thomas, Joe with Dick Vance, Roy Eldridge, and Joe Thomas. Also, Lockjaw Davis, Bobby Plater, Marshall Royal, Harold Jones, Eric [Dixon], Jimmy Crawford, [Timmie] Rogers, and Count Basie. (Box 43)
    - Torme, Mel with Billie Holliday. Also, Marilyn Monroe, Sammy Davis, Jr., Milton H. Greene, Jacques Sernas, Peggy Lee, and Judy Garland. (Box 43)
    - Turner, Trish with Cue Hodges (Box 43)
    - Turney, Norris with Russell Procope (Box 43)
    - Walker, Jim with Ralph Humphrey, Jim Lacefield, Jim Hession and Martha Hession (Box 43)
    - Wallace, Sippie with Jeannie Cheatham and "Big Mama" Thornton (Box 43)
    - Warren, Earle with Buddy Tate. Also, Rudy Rutherford, Red Bruce, Hank Jones, Tyree Glenn, Buck Clayton, Milt Hinton, Mary Osborne, Roy Eldridge, Vic Dickenson, Bud Freeman, Haywood Henry, Reuben Phillips, Bob Green, Julian Dash, Johnny Grimes, Ernie Royal, and Dud Bascomb (Box 43)
    - Washington, Jack with Joe Jones, Freddie Green, and Herschel Evans (Box 43)
    - Waters, Muddy with Johnny Winter and James Colton, 1976 (Box 43)
    - Watkins, Toney with Akma Berk, New Brookshire and Frank Racette (Box 43)
    - Webb, Spider with Carol Kaye (Box 43)
    - Webster, Benjamin with Roy Eldridge and Bill Harris. Also, Candy Ross, Argonne Thornton, Gene Ramey, and Eddie Nicholas (Box 43)
    - Wells, Dickie with Buddy Tate and others (Box 43)
    - Wess, Frank with Eric Dixon (Box 43)
    - Westbrook, Chauncey with Jo Jones (Box 43)
    - Williams, Cootie with Harry Carney. Also, Juan Tizol and Barney Bigard (Box 43)
    - Williams, Joe with Sarah Vaughan, Billy Taylor, Max Roach and Richard Stoltzman (Box 43)
    - Wilson, Chuck with Dan Barrett and Howard Alden (Box 43)
    - Wilber, Bob with [Pug] Wilber (Box 43)
    - Witherspoon, Jimmy with George Butler and Chico Hamilton (Box 43)
    - Woodman, Britt with Quentin Jackson, Clark Terry, and others (Box 43)
    - Young, Lester with Herschel Evans, Freddie Green, Buck Clayton, and Count Basie. Also, Max Kaminsky, "Hot Lips" Page, Gene Ramey, and Jo Jones (Box 43)
    - Young, Trummy with Roy Eldridge and Willie Smith. Also Kid Ory (Box 43)
    - Unidentified (Box 43)
  - Bands
    - Ailey, Alvin (Box 44)
    - Albert, Don (Box 44)
    - Allen, Jap (Box 44)
    - Alpert, Herb (Box 44)
    - Armstrong, Lil (Box 44)
    - Armstrong, Louis (Box 44)
    - Azymuth (Box 44)
    - Baker, Winfield (Box 44)
    - Barefield, Eddie (Box 44)
    - Barnet, Charlie (Box 44)
    - Bascomb, Dud (Box 44)
    - Basie, Count (Box 44)
    - Bauerle, Dick, Group (Box 44)
    - Blue Devils (Box 44)
    - Bob's Diner (Box 44)
    - Bowman, Jimmy Duo (Box 44)
    - Brubeck, Dave (Box 44)
    - Bryant, Willie (Box 44)
    - Bryants Syncopators (Box 44)
    - Cab Jivers (Box 44)
    - Calloway, Blanche (Box 44)
    - Calloway, Cab (Box 44)
    - Callender, Howard (Box 44)
    - Carolina Cotton Pickers (Box 44)
    - Carter, Benny (Box 44)
    - Carter, Chick (Box 44)
    - Celestial Navigations (Box 44)
    - Charles, Ray (Box 44)
    - Cheatham, Doc (Box 44)
    - Cole, Cozy (Box 44)
    - Corea, Chick (Box 44)
    - Crusaders (Box 44)
    - Curry, Paul (Box 44)
    - Defunkt (Box 44)
    - Delgado Brothers (Box 44)
    - Dickerson, Carroll (Box 44)
    - Dixon, George (Box 44)
    - Dizrhythmia (Box 44)
    - Duologue (Box 44)
    - Dupree, Cornell (Box 44)
    - Elgar, Larry, Manhattan Swing Orchestra (Box 44)
    - Ellington, Mercer (Box 44)
    - Elliot, Richard (Box 44)
    - Eureka Brass Band (Box 44)
    - Fattburger (Box 44)
    - Ferguson, Maynard and High Voltage (Box 44)
    - Fields, Ernie (Box 44)
    - Florida Jazz Quintet (Box 44)
    - Floyd, Troy (Box 44)
    - Freeman, Bud (Box 44)
    - Funk (Box 44)
    - Garner, Erroll (Box 44)
    - Gibson, Andy (Box 44)
    - Glascoe, Percy (Box 44)
    - Goldkettle, Jean (Box 44)
    - Grand Terrace Orchestra (Box 44)
    - Green, Lil (Box 44)
    - Griffin Bros. Orchestra (Box 44)
    - Grimes, Tiny (Box 44)
    - Hahn, Jerry (Box 44)
    - The Harlem Blues + Jazz Band (Box 44)
    - Hampton, Lionel (Box 44)
    - Hawkins, Coleman (Box 44)
    - Hawkins, Erskine (Box 44)
    - Haywood, Eddie (Box 44)
    - Henderson, Fletcher (Box 44)
    - Henderson, Horace (Box 44)
    - Herman, Woody (Box 44)
    - Hite, Les (Box 44)
    - Hopkins, Claude (Box 44)
    - Jackson, Dewey (Box 44)
    - Jackson, Franz (Box 44)
    - Jones, Jonah (Box 44)
    - Jones, Thad (Box 44)
    - Joy, Jimmie (Box 44)
    - JPJ Quartet (Box 44)
    - King, B.B. (Box 45)
    - Kinsey Report (Box 45)
    - Kirby, John (Box 45)
    - Larkin, Milton (Box 45)
    - Leaders, The (Box 45)
    - Lee, Bobby, Cotton Pickers (Box 45)
    - Lil' Ed & the Blues Imperials (Box 45)
    - Little Charlie & The Nightcats (Box 45)
    - Lunceford, Jimmie (Box 45)
    - MacDuff, Jack (Box 45)
    - Mamselles, The, 1965 (Box 45)
    - Manhattan Transfer (Box 45)
    - Martin, Sarah and her Jazz Fools (Box 44)
    - McKinney's Cotton Pickers (Box 45)
    - McShann, Jay (Box 45)
    - Millinder, Lucky (Box 45)
    - Mills Blue Rhythm Band (Box 45)
    - Modern Jazz Quartet (Box 45)
    - Mosely, Snub (Box 45)
    - Moten, Bennie (Box 45)
    - Mountain View College Lab Band (Box 45)
    - Nance's Rhythm Barons (Box 45)
    - New Orleans (Box 45)
    - Newton, Frank (Box 45)
    - New York Jazz Quartet (Box 45)
    - New York Jazz Repertory Orchestra (Box 45)
    - New York Voices (Box 45)
    - Niebla and Forcione (Box 45)
    - Nightnoise (Box 45)
    - Ohio State University Band (Box 45)
    - Olden, Clarence (Box 45)
    - Oliver, Duke (Box 45)
    - Oliver, King (Box 45)
    - Oliver, Sy (Box 45)
    - Olympia Brass Band (Box 45)
    - Paladins (Box 45)
    - Palmer, Singleton (Box 45)
    - Parker, Charlie Quartet (Box 45)
    - Pearl High School (Box 45)
    - Pillars (Box 45)
    - Pillows, Edgar (Box 45)
    - Power Tools (Box 45)
    - Preservation Hall (Box 45)
    - Previn, André (Box 45)
    - Ramey, Gene (Box 45)
    - Randall, Willie (Box 45)
    - Randi, Don, & Quest (Box 45)
    - Redman, Don (Box 45)
    - Ricardo, Ray (Box 45)
    - Rice, Eli (Box 45)
    - Road Work Ahead (Box 45)
    - Roomful of Blues (Box 45)
    - Russell, Luis (Box 45)
    - Saunders, Red (Box 45)
    - Seager, Bert (Box 45)
    - Second Sight (Box 45)
    - Siegel, Janis, & Fred Hersch (Box 45)
    - Siegel-Schwall (Box 45)
    - Simpson, Cassino (Box 45)
    - Smith, Bradley (Box 45)
    - Smith, Stuff (Box 45)
    - Snowden, Elmer (Box 45)
    - Sounds of Swing (Box 45)
    - The Staples Singers (Box 45)
    - Strunz, Jorge, & A. Farah (Box 45)
    - Symphonian Serenaders (Box 45)
    - Tangerine Dream (Box 45)
    - Tatum, Art Trio (Box 45)
    - Thomas, Joe (Box 45)
    - Thornton, Big Mama (Box 45)
    - Tinsley's Royal Aces (Box 45)
    - Tompkins, Ross Trio (Box 45)
    - Towles, Nat (Box 45)
    - Tramp-Band, 1937 (Box 45)
    - Trent, Alphonse (Box 45)
    - TRPTS (Box 45)
    - Virginia Ravens (Box 45)
    - Walking Wounded (Box 45)
    - Waller, Fats (Box 45)
    - Washington, Booker T. (Box 45)
    - Welsh, Alex (Box 45)
    - Whyte, Zack + his Chocolate Beau Brummels (Box 45)
    - Widespread Depression Orchestra (Box 45)
    - Wilson, Irene, Orchestra (Box 45)
    - Windows (Box 45)
    - World's Greatest Jazz Band of Yank Lawson + Bob Haggart (Box 45)
  - Earl Hines
    - Early Years to 1939 (Box 46)
    - 1940's (Box 46)
    - 1950's (Box 46)